<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Home</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>googlesites</title>
      <link>/projects/googlesites/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/googlesites/</guid>
      <description>Overview How to Get Started Add a page from HTML Find your Content Upload an Attachment to your Page Delete your Page  Additional Features Questions Support   Overview The googlesites package is the R implementation of the Google Sites API. Using this package assumes you’ve used the Web UI to create your site. Once you’ve got a site (and maybe some templates), you can use this package to add more content, add attachments, find content, and delete content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rdfp</title>
      <link>/projects/rdfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/rdfp/</guid>
      <description>Overview Features How to Get Started Install rdfp Library Setup and Authenticate Check Current User Info Setup Custom Fields for Items Setup Custom Targeting Keys and Values Create an Order Get Line Items By A Filter Run a Report  Check out the Tests Credits License Questions Support   Overview The rdfp package is the R implementation of the Double Click for Publishers (DFP) API and similar in comparison to the existing client libraries supported by Google.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>roas</title>
      <link>/projects/roas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/roas/</guid>
      <description>Overview Features Functions How to Get Started Install roas Library Setup and Authenticate Authenticate with oas_build_credentials() Listing OAS Objects Reading an OAS Object Running Reports Getting Inventory Forecasts  Questions Support   Overview The roas package is the R implementation of the Open Ad Stream (OAS) API. I created the package because very few tools and documentation exist for the OAS API.
View source code on GitHub at: https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>